all right I'm here with Charles Staley
um now Charles is my training partner
he's been doing barbell hip thrust for
over a year now yeah and he's been doing
barbell hip thrust for over a year even
got up to
550 620 620 620 it's on video yeah but
uh this is the first time he used bands
and I want to tell you about his
reaction because this is the way most
people react the first time they use
band so Charles you just finished using
bands for the first time what do you
think yeah I'm still I mean I think I
finished the set like 5 minutes ago and
I'm still like cramped and uh I'm like
my the famous story with me is I just
never feel glutes on anything I feel
hamstrings on squats deadlifts I just
pulled a 495 deadlift about 20 minutes
ago never felt anything in my glutes
I've I've hip thrusted 455 for 12 never
felt my glutes but we just strapped uh
two of these bands on here and uh I just
told Brett a few minutes ago that if if
I was you trying to sell this unit I
would just really push the bands because
I just did a set of I think I actually I
did eight reps with two bands and I've
never honestly it is probably the first
time I've actually felt my glutes doing
anything and I'm a 400 squatter or a 500
puller so uh at what age uh at 54 yeah
so um so my glutes are not entirely uh
connective tissue and Scar Tissue so uh
there is there's still some hope but
yeah that was really caught my attention